<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MachBio</title><link>http://machb.io/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://machb.io/feeds/sandeep-shantharam.rss.xml" rel="self"></atom:link><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:17:34 -0400</lastBuildDate><item><title>Content Manager</title><link>http://machb.io/2019/09/14/content-manager/</link><description>
  &lt;!-- Include the script that builds the page and powers Netlify CMS --&gt;
  &lt;script src="https://unpkg.com/netlify-cms@^2.0.0/dist/netlify-cms.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Sandeep Shantharam</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:17:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>tag:machb.io,2019-09-14:2019/09/14/content-manager/</guid></item><item><title>Blogging Without any Dependencies</title><link>http://machb.io/2015/05/01/blogging-without-any-dependencies/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;After several years of trying out different platforms of blogging - Blogger (Google), Wordpress (Automattic), Octopress (Jekyll) - found it frustrated with the broken dependencies or feature limitation due to the hosted solution. I have finally decided to setup this blog with my favourite programming language - Python using the framework - Pelican for which I have the confidence to fix the code myself if there is any dependencies being broken in the future. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But you said, you have been blogging for so long, where are the previous blog posts..?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am shameful of them, being busy in graduate school and working as a software developer in one of the top Indian software company, I have developed the experience which has made me more mature to the world around me and coming to a completely new country (United States of America) has given me an opportunity to shape myself to a person who is more logical and sensitive in his expression. This blog will be more aligned to thoughts and happenings of mature speaking his mind with all the technical as well as personal opinions on this blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To travel is to discover that everyone is wrong about other countries. &amp;nbsp;— Aldous Huxley&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Sandeep Shantharam</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>tag:machb.io,2015-05-01:2015/05/01/blogging-without-any-dependencies/</guid><category>blogging</category><category>introduction</category></item></channel></rss>